wakeworld.com 2000-12-04

# WakeWorld Privacy Policy

   **WakeWorld Home**

   **Equipment and**  
   **Training**  
    Board Guide  
    Binding Guide  
    Product Reviews  
    Fins  
    Pylon Extensions  
    Bigger Wakes  
    Frequently Asked Q's  
    Trick List  
    Training/Camps

   **Events**  
    Pro Events  
    Pro Standings  
    TV Schedule  
    Boardstock  

   **Online Community**  
    Online Tournament  
    Discussion Board  
    Rider Link  
    Classifieds  

   **Features**  
    News, News, News  
    Interviews  
    Contests  
    Cool Links  
    Article Archives  

   **Other Stuff**  
    Take Our Survey  
    Get WakeWorld Gear  
    Advertise on WakeWorld  
    Terms of Use  
    Privacy Policy  

 |  Visit our Sponsor by clicking on the banner below...    

### _WakeWorld Privacy Policy_

We respect the privacy of our mailing list subscribers, those who answer our surveys and those who enter our contests and Online Tournament. 

It is our policy: 

  * To respect the purpose for which our site visitors gave us information. We give users choice and consent over how their personal information is used, and remove names immediately upon request. 
  * To not sell, rent, or loan our lists to third parties for e-mail marketing. While we sell advertising in our e-mail publications to other companies, we do not allow third parties any other use of our lists. 
  * To send our periodicals only to those who request them, and immediately unsubscribe those who request it. Sometimes people subscribe for their friends, and while we cannot prevent that, our welcome message to subscribers -- and every issue of our free newsletters -- explain how to subscribe. We keep our subscription lists as clean as possible to prevent obsolete e-mails to take unnecessary bandwidth. 
  * To store subscriber and password files with personal information in a secure manner. We store such files in areas not accessible to Web browsers, behind password protection, or off-line. 

If you have any questions about this policy, please email us at [Contact@WakeWorld.com](mailto:contact@wakeworld.com) and we'll answer all your questions.
